as you know, a lot of months from now.
>> Um, yeah, first off, rehab's going great
so far. You know, just um hitting all
the checkpoints that the doctor wants
you to do and getting the strength and
the the range um of mobility back. Um,
so that's been going great. Been doing
um all of it here in Kansas City so far.
And um Julie has been crushing it,
pushing me. And um the doctor kind of
gives you like goals to get to and I
just try to maximize those and they they
hold me back because I always want to go
a little bit further. So, um, it's been
going great. I mean, obviously, I think
the the long term, um, I mean, I want to
be ready for week one. Um, doctor said
that I could be, but I can't predict,
um, what's going to happen throughout
the process, but that's my goal. And so,
I'll, uh, try to prepare myself to be
ready to play in that week one and, and
have no restrictions. You know, you want
to be out there healthy and and giving
us the best chance to win. And so, um,
obviously hopefully be able to do some
some stuff in OTAAS and then get to
training camp and and hopefully be able
to do a lot there. So, um, I'm excited
for the the process. It's a long
process, but I'm excited for it.
>> Let's go next to Sam McDow.
>> Hey, Patrick. Um, just wondering just
you mentioned uh OTAAS and training
camp. You know, you guys have layer on
to your playbook every year. I don't
know whether you'll have new voices in
the room with with coaches or whatnot,
but regardless, I know you guys will at
least change up some things offensively.
How will you keep up to speed on that?
And obviously you did this as a rookie.
I just wonder if you might lean on that
experience at all.
>> Yeah, I think I think more than anything
it's just it's just being in there,
being in the room, being on the field as
much as they'll let me and then when I'm
not able to to take the reps, kind of
getting those mental reps behind the
play and seeing everything develop. Um
um the coaches will will put me in the
right position in order to do that. Um
but I I take it slow, but at the same
time, I'll push to be out there as much
as I can be. Um, and so, uh, we have a
great plan in place, um, as far as kind
of where we want to get to. Um, but we
have to let it all play out and kind of
take it a day at a time. Um, which, uh,
uh, has been hard for me, but at the
same time, it makes me get the best out
of every single day.
>> We, we just haven't been able to talk to
you since the injury for obvious
reasons, but just wonder what was that
moment like for you on the field?
>> Um, yeah. I mean, obviously I I knew
something had happened. Um, but once I
was able to walk a little bit, I I
thought I might have a chance to kind of
get back into the game. um uh you kind
of go into the tent, they do the test
and they want to take you back to the
locker room. And so I you you don't know
for sure and everything like that, but
when I was able to move, I I I asked one
of the doctors if I'd get a brace and
just just finish the game, but they
wouldn't let me. Um and so they uh um
obviously it kind of sunk in once I the
game ended and then I was able to get
the results from the MRI and stuff like
that. Um which is it's hard, but at the
same time got to kind of flip the script
fast knowing that it's going to be a
quick turnaround to get to this season.
And so now it's just been motivating
trying to push myself to like I said the
much as much as they'll let me push
myself to be ready for next year.
>> We'll go next to Herby Top. Go ahead
Herby.
>> Hey Patrick, happy new year. Sid, I have
two quick questions here real quick.
Patrick, you mentioned you're you're
sort of eyeing OTAAS, but like every
year in April during the offseason
workout program, you've you've attempted
to bring the guys down there to Texas
with you. How is this process going to
affect what you normally do with your
receivers?
>> Um, I mean, I can't speak for what coach
Reed exactly is going to do, but I I
would expect us to kind of be here a
little bit earlier just with me already
being here. Um, I've talked to some of
the receivers already. I mean, I think
that's kind of the mindset that we have
is we want to be in the building and and
getting back to it. And I mean, the
thing about um when you lose and you
don't make the playoffs, you have a
longer offseason than you usually have.
And so I think guys are getting away
right now. Um kind of getting their
minds right, getting their bodies right.
Um but guys are hungry to get back out
there. I mean it's hard to watch these
playoff games and so um we'll be in the
building and you'll try to build that
camaraderie that way is just doing stuff
around Kansas City, maybe taking to some
Royals games or whatever wherever that
is and try to build that those
relationships with those guys and then
being in the building you'll be able to
get the same work that you would have
got kind of down there in Texas. And
Patrick, you mentioned this season. You
I'm sure you've had an opportunity now
to actually look back at what has
happened. What What went wrong in 2025
in your opinion?
>> Yeah, I think just compounding mistakes.
I mean, you you make mistakes throughout
a game. I for myself, I look at some of
the red zone interceptions I threw and
kind of bigger moments in the third and
fourth quarter of games. I mean, that's
stuff that I hadn't done in the past.
And so, um, speaking for myself, just
trying to be better in those moments.
And then um I think offensively we
weren't consistent enough um throughout
games. We had stretches in games where
we played good. We had stretches in the
season where we played really good, but
we got to be better. And um that starts
with me and then it kind of has to feed
throughout the entire offense. Um and so
um I think like I said, guys are
motivated. Um coaches, um players, we're
all motivated to be better this next
year. And um like like I said, it sucks
watching these games. I mean, I want to
be out there playing football and um
especially at this time of year is the
best time of year to play football. So,
um, it'll give us the motivation
hopefully for us to come back stronger
next year.
>> We'll go next to Todd Lebo.
>> Got a couple quick ones here as well.
You know that Pat Patrick, you mentioned
the offense. Just a couple things here
and there, but does this feel like to
you like there just a couple little
tweaks or is there need to be some sort
of a kind of an overhaul to the offense?
What sort of things do you think the
offense needs to do here while you guys
have a little extra time that you're not
used to having? Yeah, I mean you just
got to dive deep into that scheme
evaluation and see what teams are seeing
against us. I think um the the the one
part about having so much success is
teams watch a lot of film on you. Um and
so they try to have good game plans on
how to combat what you do and what
you've done well. And um you saw that
this year where teams were were very
conscious of the plays that we've hit
for a long time. And so we have to find
ways to counteract that and kind of go
at go at teams and um be able to utilize
that and make more explosive plays. I
think if we can get back to some of that
stuff um as as well as being consistent
um on a downto- basis um that that
that'll be stuff that we got to continue
to get better at and I think um there's
minor tweaks but at the same time you
got to have to you got to look at the
entire picture and see if we can be
better at every single area. So um we'll
see where we get to after watching the
film but I'm willing to do whatever it
takes in order to go out there and have
success.
>> And it looks like you may lose your
coordinator Matt Naggie's taken some
head coaching interviews and is not
under contract next year. I mean, what
what did he mean to you these last few
years and early on when you had him as
well? If if he's not gonna be around,
what will that be like?
>> Yeah, I mean, I love coach Naggie and
he's done a lot of great things in my
career to help me become the quarterback
that I am. And I know that he's looking
to take that that step and get back to
the head coaching uh spot and um I hope
he gets another opportunity to do that.
Um but he's like a great man, a great
person. Um it's been cool to see like
the the changes of him as a coach as um
him going to be a head coach and coming
back, but he gave me a lot of ideas to
to be better as a person, as a
quarterback. And so I'm hoping the best
for him as he goes through this head
coaching process and he gets another
opportunity to go out there and lead an
organization.
>> We'll go next to Vah.
>> Hey Patrick, thanks for making time. Um
just a clarification first. Is your
surgery more accurately called a a
repair or a reconstruction? Did are you
able to articulate that? Then I'll just
have a followup.
>> Um, honestly, like both of them I feel
like mean the same thing. But I I think
um I think what I got from my doctor
would that kind of cleared it up for me
is obviously I had the ACL and the LCL,
but it everything else was clean. And so
like as bad as it was, it was as clean
as it could be. There was no there's a
lot of I found out there's a lot of
little things that could happen around
that knee that I had never even known.
So, uh, I I was lucky enough, God
blessed me enough to not do some of
those little things that could prolong
the injury. So, now it's just about
rehabbing that rehabbing and getting the
LCL and the ACL right, giving them time,
giving it time to rest. Um, but at the
same time, building up that strength so
that whenever I am ready to go, I'm
ready to go.
>> And just with that, I you know, you've
talked so much about already about how
much you're pushing yourself. Is there
any kind of balance or challenge to
thinking about your urgency to get back
versus, you know, really thinking long
term for your for your future years from
now?
>> Yeah, for sure. I mean, that's that's
something that I have to think of. I
think the coaches and the organization
all has to think of. Um, but at the same
time, that's why they give me limits to
where I can push it. It's like that Dr.
Cooper did. He described that to me. He
said, "I'll give you the limits of where
you can push it to, and then it's up to
you how far you want to push it to that
limit." And knowing me, that's I'm gonna
push it to that exact limit every single
day. And so, um, you you there's places
you can't go yet, which I want to, but I
can't go yet. But at the same time, um,
they're doing it for a reason. And that
that starts with Dr. Cooper and his
team. That starts with the with Julie
and Rick and all them in the training
room. And, uh, it kind of feeds
throughout the entire organization.
>> Thanks, Patrick.
>> Let's go next to Matt McMullen.
>> Hey, Patrick. Um, you mentioned Julie.
You've obviously worked with her a lot
over the years. How important is that
relationship when you're going through
something like this?
>> Yeah, I think I think it's extremely
important because what I found out
throughout this process is not every day
is going to feel amazing. Like there's
some days you're going to be sore.
There's some days you're going to feel
stiff, but you have to have someone that
you trust that's going to get the best
out of you that's going to keep you
safe. And um someone that's going to
push you. I think that's what's more
than anything. It's um some days I want
to go in there and crush rehab, some
days I just want to get through it. She
doesn't let you have the get through it
day. She pushes you to be the best every
single day. And um it's been a different
process kind of jumping right into
working out like this. Like I always
worked out kind of built up throughout
the offseason, but um it's been fun to
at least be with people that um care
about me and and that want to push me to
be the best that I can be. And so uh um
I'm in that training room every single
day and I'm trying to make sure that uh
that I'm I'm ready to go as quickly as
possible.
>> Let's go next to Matt Derek.
>> Patrick, appreciate your time. And two
questions for you. Juan, you mentioned,
you know, working with Julie and being
here in Kansas City. Is your expectation
that you're going to do the majority or
all of your rehab on this knee here in
Kansas City and and how do you imagine
that working with the work that you also
do with Bobby on your own?
>> Yeah, we've actually already had a good
plan and we've kind of I met with Julian
with Bobby and Rick and and and the
whole team and I I'll be here mostly um
in Kansas City. Um there'll be times I
will be in Dallas. I mean, just with
meeting with Dr. Cooper and and being
with his team as well. But um it's been
great to see the the collaboration with
everybody so that we have a plan for
every single day that I have this
offseason and you got to maximize all
those days. And so um a lot of it will
be in Kansas City. There'll be times
where Rick Julie might be down in Dallas
with Dr. Cooper helping me out there as
well. Um but uh I'm doing whatever I can
to maximize every day. So we have a good
plan that we've talked through every
single day of this entire offseason.
And with regards to Matt and the
possibility he could leave you, what are
the things that you want and that you
like and having in an offensive
coordinator that are important to you,
those traits? And is there anybody that
is on your mind that you'd love to see
as your offensive coordinator one day?
>> Um, I mean, obviously there's there's
names out there, but I think with
especially how many vacancies there is
at the head coaching uh job, you kind of
have to let that all play out to see um
how you kind of build your build the
staff. But I don't know coach Reed um if
if coach if coach Nag is able to get
another job a head coaching job that
he'll have a good plan of who he wants
to bring in. Um but for my for me I just
want someone that that that that loves
football that cares about football that
wants to give everything they can to win
um to hold people accountable and then
to bring new ideas every single day. I
think that's something that we have to
continue to do if you want to continue
to be great um in this in this league is
you have to continue to evolve and get
better and better. And um that's
something that we will try to do here.
And um I want to get back to that
winning culture of being accountable to
each other and and going out there and
playing great football uh every single
day, practice or game.
>> We only have time for one more. We're
going to wrap it up with Matt Foster
real quick. Thank you, Patrick.
>> Patrick, real quick. Um, we've talked a
lot about the physical side and the
challenges that come with a rehab like
this, but how are you going about the
mental toll that a serious injury takes
like this? And again, wanting to push
your body to certain limits, but you
kind of have to take it back um until
it's ready to do what you want it to do.
>> Yeah. No, I mean, it definitely weighs
on your mental a little bit. Um, but for
me, I think just having that goal in
mind of of trying to get better every
day and knowing what I'm I'm striving to
do is which is to be ready as quickly as
possible and have a chance to play in
that um that opening day game um no
matter where it is so that so that I'm
there with my teammates and and can be
at training camp and and doing what I
need to do. Uh, I think that's kind of
pushed me through some of those mental
hurdles and that as well as having a
great wife that that is able to keep me
involved with the with the kids and um
the kids understand that dad can't
necessarily be the the dad that I
usually am throwing them around the
couches and stuff like that, but I I'm
there and I'm trying to and doing stuff
like that. I think that's uh that's been
good for my mental is just being around
the kids and being around the family and
having a lot of great people around me.
>> Thank you, Patrick. That's all I have
for you.
>> Thank you all. Appreciate you.